Finding Aid for University of Michigan Photographs Vertical File ca. 1817-1995
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Class Photos, 1858-1956
  - Classes by Year: Group portraits and reunions
    - Class of 1921
      - Law (Folder F99-527)
    - Class of 1922
      - Law (Folder F99-527a)
    - Class of 1923
      - Engineering (Folder F99-L)
    - Class of 1924
      - Engineering (Folder F99-527b)
    - Class of 1926
      - Dental (Folder F99-527c)
    - Class of 1927
      - Law (Folder F99-528)
      - Architecture (Folder F99-528)
    - Class of 1928
      - Law (Folder F99-529)
      - Nursing (Folder F99-529)
      - Medical (Folder F99-529)
        large
    - Class of 1929
      - Law (Folder F99-L)
    - Class of 1930
      - Law (Folder F99-L)
    - Class of 1931
      - Law (Folder F99-L)
    - Class of 1932
      - Law (Folder F99-L)
    - Class of 1933
      - Law (Folder F99-M)
    - Class of 1934
      - Engineering (Folder F99-529a)
      - Law (Folder F99-L)
    - Class of 1935
      - Law (Folder F99-L)
    - Class of 1936
      - Engineering (Folder F99 529a)
      - Law (Folder F99-L)
    - Class of 1938
      - Law (Folder F99-L)
      - Mechanical Engineering (Folder F99-529b)
    - Class of 1939
      - Law (Folder F99-L)
    - Class of 1940
      - Law (Folder F99-M)
    - Class of 1942
      - Law (Folder F99-L)
    - Class of 1943/44
      - Law (Folder F99-530)
    - Class of 1949
      - Law (Folder F99-M)
    - Class of 1953
      - Law (Folder F99-531)
      - Dental (Folder F99-531)
    - Classes of 1955 and 1956
      - Law (Folder F99-M)
  - Classes by Year, Individuals
    (Individual portraits, many unidentified by name)
    - Class of 1860 (Folder F99-532)
    - Class of 1866 (Folder F99-533)
    - Class of 1873 (Folder F99-534)
    - Class of 1874 (Folder F99-535)
    - Class of 1875 (Folder F99-536)
    - Class of 1876 (Folder F99-537)
    - Class of 1878 (Folder F99-538)
    - Class of 1883 (Folder F99-539)
    - Class of 1890 (Folder F99-540)
    - Class of 1898 (Folder F99-541)
    - Class of 1903 (Folder F99-542)
    - Class of 1904, 2 folders (Folder F99-543-544)
    - Class of 1905 (Folder F99-545)
    - Class of 1950 (Folder F99-545a)
- Affiliated and Associated Organizations
  The series Affiliated and Associated Organizations is comprised of photographs of a number of regional alumni clubs, faculty and staff organizations, musical societies, and student ROTC groups. Individual files may include photos of the organizations officers, staff or activities.
  - The Emeritus Club of the University of Michigan Alumni Association (Folder H1d-546)
  - Alumni reunions (Folder H4-M)
  - University of Michigan Clubs: Miscellaneous (Folder H6a-547)
  - University of Michigan Club of New York (Folder H6a-M)
  - University of Michigan Club of Rochester (Folder H6a-M)
  - Apostles Club (Folder M3-M)
  - Faculty Women's Club (Folder M3-548)
  - Goose Quill Club (Folder M3-M)
  - Quadrangle Club (Folder M3-549)
  - Scientific Club (Folder M3-550)
  - Black Faculty and Staff Association (Folder M6-551)
  - University Musical Society (Folder N1-N)
  - May Festival, 2 folders (Folder N3-552-553)
  - R.O.T.C. (Folder N10-M)
  - N.R.O.T.C. (Folder N11-M)
  - International Congress of Orientalists, 1967 (Folder N301-554)